Guide to the Here is New York Collection 1996-2007 (bulk 2001-2002) PR 258
New-York Historical Society
- Series VI: WTC: The First Twenty-Four Hours
  DVDs and VHS copies of WTC: The First Twenty-Four Hours, directed by Etienne Sauret and David Carrara (72 DVDs, 1 VHS). Here is new york was not involved in the production of this film. Copies were sold for charitable purposes at some here is new york exhibitions.
  Public access copies available; DVD can be played on HINY computer terminal.
  - 2 public access copies of DVD, 2001 (Box CD3)
  - 65 DVDs, 1 VHS, 2001 (Box WTC1)
  - 5 defective, returned DVDs, 2001 (Box WTC2)
  - Housing for 2 public access copies, 2001 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Return invoice--Buchhandlung Walther Konig gallery, Berlin, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Series VII: Added Material
  This series contains material related to the here is new york project, but not created by the original organization or for original exhibitions. Here is new york images continue to be exhibited.
  - Louisville Free Public Library: Exhibit Responses [copies] Donated by Louisville Free Public Library, 2006 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - The New-York Historical Society: Exhibit Transcripts of Voices of 9.11 testimonies used in exhibit "Here is New York: Remembering 9/11" (testimonies were edited for exhibition), 2007 (Box 75, Folder 4)